ACTWU's General Executive Board (GEB) Records 5619/030
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Department of Labor, Employment Regulations on Learners pg. 1-100, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Regulations Applicable to the Employment of Learners in the Single Pants, Shirts and Allied Garments, Women's Apparel, Sportswear, Rainwear, Robes and Leather and Sheep-lined Garments Division of the Apparel Industry
- Department of Labor, Employment Regulations on Learners pg. 101-200, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Department of Labor, Employment Regulations on Learners pg. 201-300, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Retail Division Activity Report, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Retail Division Activity Report Mailing Lists, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Retail Drive, Expense Accounts, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Retail Division, Shopping Center Organizing Campaign, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board, Industry Committee No. 76, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Laundry Workers Union, Local #432 and American Coat, Apron and Linen Supply Laundry, Inc., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Retail Clerks, Housing Development, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Retail Clerks International Association, Activity, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Retail Clerks, Spartan Atlantic, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board, Spanish Classes, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Spartan Department Stores, Contracts, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Sagner International, Inc., 1963-1967 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Spartan Department Stores, Grievances, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Atlantic Spartan Merger, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Charges against Giuseppe Procopio, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Resignations, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Shirt and Boys' Waist Workers Union, Letters on Charges against Alex Cohen, 1922-1924 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Hearing, Statements by Miller and Wetscher, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Charges against Harry Cohen, 1921-1924 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Letters on Howard Clothes, Inc., 1931 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Bank, Grievances on Misuse of Funds, 1929-1931 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Investigation of Local #4, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  Disappearance of Funds in the Unemployment Fund
- Miscellaneous Receipts, 1920-1931 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Confidential Memoranda, 1916-1928 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Local #4, 1927-1929 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  Conference Records
- General Executive Board, Charges against Tony Parish, 1942-1946 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  New Orleans Joint Board
- New Orleans Joint Board, Loans to Tony Parish, 1941-1945 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Amalgamated Bank, Letters from Max Loenthal, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Investigation Committee, Report on the Case of Louis Stark, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Children's Clothing Matter, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Cases and Hearings, 1916-1929 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Retail, Department Stores, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Ricardo Corp. and Carlita Corp., 1964-1971 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- General Executive Board, Clothing Negotiations, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  Resolutions for the incoming GEB by the 27th Biennial Convention
- Laundry Workers' Union Local #432 and American Coat, Apron & Linen Supply, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Edro Corp., 1961-1968 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Caribe Sports Co., Inc. (Rawlings Corp.), 1961-1966 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Waycross Sportswear, Inc. (Arlan's), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- IUD Puerto Rican Committee, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Puerto Rican Farm Worker Problem in California, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union and Southland Manufacturing Corp., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- The Labor Union, Newspaper Clippings, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  Hillman and Communist Ties
- International Glove Workers Union, 1937-1939 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  Resolutions on Affiliation with the ACWA